radioshackwireless.com 2011-11-09

# RadioShack.com Helpdesk

The following Privacy Policy applies only to the RadioShack.com web site and information provided by you or otherwise collected online through RadioShack.com. For the privacy policies applicable to information collected in our stores or by other means, see the sign posted in stores titled, "We Value Our Relationship." 

**We are concerned about privacy**  
Your privacy is very important to us. RadioShack respects and protects the privacy of its visitors. In this document, we explain how we use the information you supply us. If we update our privacy policy, all revisions will be posted on this page. We reserve the right to change the privacy policy at any time. 

**Information collection and use**  
Two types of information may be collected when you visit our web site, information that you knowingly provide us (called personally identifiable information), and information that is obtained from your visit but is not directly associated with you (called non-personally identifiable information). 

**Personally identifiable information**  
Personally identifiable information may include information that you provide to us by requesting information, when registering for special offers or programs or when you purchase products online. This may include your name, address (including billing and shipping addresses), telephone number, e-mail address, organization, city, state and zip code. We may use this information, to process and ship orders, to contact you about the status of your order, to contact you with answers to your questions, or to provide information about new and exciting products, services, promotions and corporate-related information. We may use mailings, telephone calls and e-mail to contact you. 

You also may create an account through RadioShack.com at any time by providing your email address and creating a unique password. An account is not required to visit our site or to place an order through RadioShack.com. Creating an account allows you to save order information, order history, track the status of your orders and set your ordering preferences. For your privacy and security, we do not store credit card or Gift Card numbers in your account. You may change saved account information at anytime. Simply visit the Your Account page, log in with your email address and password. 

For those customers who purchase products from us online, additional personally identifiable information such as credit card information will be collected. This information is collected in order to process your order. 

For those customers who register for special email offerings, we may use the zip code you provided to email special offers that apply only to your area. 

We are committed to the protection of the privacy of our customers and visitors. While in the checkout process of our online store, we make use of 128 bit encryption via digital IDs provided and certified by [VeriSign, Inc.](http://www.verisign.com/) These IDs enable our commerce site to conduct authenticated, strongly encrypted online commerce. Customers can submit credit card numbers or other personal information to our site with the assurance that they are doing business with us (not an impostor's "spoof" of our site) and that the information which they are sending to us cannot be intercepted or decrypted by anyone else. 

**Requesting removal of your information**  
If you have registered for special e-mail offerings, you may unsubscribe from the program, by visiting the [e-mail unsubscribe page](http://www.radioshack.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?subdisplay=unsubscribe&display=account) or click on the links available at the bottom of any of these special offer e-mails. You may also request the removal of your information by [contacting us via e-mail](http://www.radioshack.com/helpdesk/index.jsp?stillHaveQuestion=yes&subdisplay=contact&display=store). 

If you wish to receive more personalized information from RadioShack or change anything about your profile such as your interests or e-mail format, please click on the links available at the bottom of any of these special offer e-mails or visit the Your Account page. 

**Non-personally identifiable information**  
Non-personally identifiable information is collected without any direct association with you specifically. In the normal course of using RadioShack.com, we may collect information about your habits and usage of our sites. 

Our web sites may contain technologies known as action tags, web beacons or 1x1 pixel gifs. These employ a common internet technique used to compile aggregated statistics about the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns, common navigation paths within the sites, types of browsers and platforms that access the sites and the average connection speeds used to connect to the sites. This information is used to enhance the online experience of our customers. These technologies do not use or collect personally identifiable information, such as names or address, and do not link online actions to an identifiable person. 

An IP address is a number that is assigned to your computer when you are using the Internet. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. RadioShack collects IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, to report aggregated information and to audit the use of our site. If we are required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena, we will provide these IP addresses to the proper authorities. 

**Information sharing and disclosure**  
Agents, employees and contractors of RadioShack who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy and the high standards of the corporation. 

  * Information about you specifically will not be used for any purpose other than to carry out the services you requested from RadioShack and its affiliates. All of our affiliates have agreed to maintain the security and confidentiality of the information we provide to them.
  * We will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone at any time.
  * We will not use any personal information beyond what is necessary to assist us in delivering to you the services you have requested.
  * We may send personally identifiable information about you to other organizations when:

|  | 

  * We have your consent to share the information (you will be provided the opportunity to opt-out if you desire). For example, if you opt-in for emails we will share this information with our marketing provider.
  * We need to share your information in order to provide the product or service you have requested. For example, we need to share information with credit card providers and shippers to bill and ship the product you requested.
  * We are required to do so by law, for example, in response to a court order or subpoena.

---|---  
  
**Use of Cookies and Applets**  
Cookies and applets are small text files that are placed on your computer's hard drive by our servers to identify your computer. Cookies and applets are only read by the domain that placed them there and are unable to execute any code or virus. We may use cookies or applets to recognize you when you visit our sites, to personalize your experience and generally to serve you better. We do not use cookies or applets to track your activities once you leave our web site. 

You may delete these files from your computer at any time. You can set your web browser to notify you if such information is about to be placed on your computer, and you can choose the option in your web browser to refuse it. If you refuse the information, you may not be able to make full use of the features on our web site. 

**Kids under 13 years of age**  
RadioShack.com does not seek to collect identification information about kids under 13 years of age. If we discover such information, we will delete it. Thus, we typically retain no identifiable information about kids. However, if a parent believes his/her child has provided us information, simply call and that we delete it. In order for us to find the information in our databases, you will need to provide us with the following information which will only be used to search our databases and deliver confirmation to you: 

  * Parent's Name
  * Address
  * Telephone Number
  * Email Address (for confirmation)
  * The name of the child (if you suspect a nickname was used, please provide it)
  * If the child shares time at two addresses, you will need to provide us the second address also, along with any email addresses for the child.

In order to request deletion of identifiable information that RadioShack may have unintentionally collected about your child, please call **(817)415-3200**. Please inform the service agent that you wish to delete your child's information, and supply the service agent with the necessary information as stated above.   
Confirmation that information which identifies your child has been deleted will be delivered to you by e-mail, regular mail, or telephone.   
PLEASE NOTE: Deleting your child's information will likely make it impossible for us to notify you or your child in the event of a recall of a product he or she purchased in violation of our policies. So if your child purchased ANYTHING from us in spite of our efforts to prevent it, you may not wish to delete all information. Instead, you may simply request that we correct the information by correcting the name in our records to your name rather than your child's.   
In consideration of young users, it is our intention to adhere to the [Better Business Bureau's "Children Advertising Review Unit" (CARU) guidelines](http://www.caru.org/), including its guidelines on advertising. When you communicate with RadioShack, we make every effort to ensure your privacy and safety. As an added precaution, however, we still encourage parents to monitor their child's use of the Internet, and to help us protect their privacy by reminding them never to exchange personal information with this or any other web site without the assistance or express written permission of a parent or other responsible adult. 

**Links to and from RadioShack.com**  
Our web site contains links to and from other web sites that are not operated or controlled by RadioShack. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE PRIVACY PRACTICES OF, AND USE OF CHILDREN'S PERSONAL INFORMATION BY, WEB SITES THAT WE DO NOT OPERATE, and our privacy policy does not apply to these sites. 

**"Email a Friend" or "Email your Wish List"**  
If you elect to use our "Email a Friend" or "Email your Wish List" service for informing a friend about our site or products you are interested in, we may ask for your email address, your name, the email address and the name of your friend. RadioShack will automatically send the friend a one-time email on your behalf. RadioShack does not store this information. It is only used for the sole purpose of sending this one time email. 

**We will not condition access or participation in an activity**  
RadioShack will not condition a user's access or participation in an activity on giving out more personal information than what is considered reasonably necessary for the activity. 

**Co-branded offers**  
From time-to-time RadioShack.com provides some co-branded offers, for example to apply for a RadioShack Credit Card or to manage your AnswersPlus Account. In these cases the user is directed to another party's website. The use of data collected through that website is governed by it's own privacy policies. 

**Sweepstakes and contests**  
From time-to-time, we may request information from you through contests or sweepstakes. Participation in these contests or sweepstakes is completely voluntary and the user has a choice whether or not to participate. Information requested may include contact information (such as name, address and phone number). Contact information gathered from contests and sweepstakes will be used to notify the winners and award prizes. We use a third party to pick the contests and sweepstakes winners (please see the Information sharing and disclosure section for details on third parties). Demographic information such as the users birthdate may be requested, this is used to validate the age of the contestant when the rules of the contest specify a minimum age requirement. Users who enter the contest may also choose to receive marketing communications from RadioShack. The user may elect to "opt-out" of this communication at the bottom of each email or by visiting the Requesting removal of your information section of this policy. 

**How changes to the privacy policy will be communicated**  
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the homepage, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

If however, we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users by posting a notice on our web site for 30 days. 

If users have questions or concerns regarding this statement, they should contact RadioShack Online Privacy by email [RadioShack.Online.Privacy@radioshack.com](mailto:RadioShack.Online.Privacy@radioshack.com).
